Miss Cecil? May?
But why...?
We're here to bring you back home, Mariabell.
How did you two get here?
Yes, about that...
Meddling in my affairs...
When Hinata and I were this close to...
I was so close...
Unacceptable...
Tears of blood?!
Unforgiveable...
I stepped in to save Lord Hinata
because you were about to pounce on him.
Excuse me?!
Hey, calm down, ladies!
May?!
Sorry for barging in on you.
But I think we oughtta move our reunion
somewhere more private.
What's going on?
Are they filming a TV drama?
A fight scene?
Good idea. Let's get out of here.
It's nice to see you again, Miss Cecil.
Indeed.
And I'm glad you're doing well, May.
Sure am, thanks!
Miss Cecil is a priestess who
serves the gods,
and May is a demi-human girl.
Thanks for the coffee.
Huh, so this is what our
little Hinata's house looks like!
First you show up uninvited, then you crash
mine and Hinata's sacred love nest?
The audacity!
Lord Hinata said that this would be
the best place for us to chat uninterrupted.
Besides, whose fault is it that we're
even in this situation to begin with?
What situation?
Do you have any idea the chaos you've caused
by coming here all willy-nilly?!
Huh?
The existence of the other world
was once meant to be a secret.
If it were to become widespread knowledge,
we don't know how our two worlds
might influence each other.
We were dispatched on government orders
to retrieve you before something
goes horribly wrong.
No way...
I'm sorry. I really was rooting
for the two of you.
If you leave now,
you'll be pardoned due to your
commendable victory over the Demon Lord.
So come quietly—
No!
This whole thing is a plot to try and
separate me and Hinata, isn't it?!
Your tricks won't work on me!
She didn't listen to a single thing I said!
C-Can't breathe...
You can't have him!
B-Bell?!
Hinata and I are destined to be together!
I won't let anyone tear us apart.
He's the only thing I need.
The government or an entire world...
I won't tolerate anything
that stands in our way.
I see. That settles it, then.
You're going to leave us alone?
No. If I can't convince you,
then I'll have to use force.
Wha— Miss Cecil, take it easy!
Fine...
I was never a big fan of yours
in the first place.
Always poking your nose in
other people's business...
What, do you really hate dark elves that much?
No, not at all.
In fact, I have a lot of respect for
dark elves and their virtuous mentality.
However...
that excludes you.
SNAP
You and that humongous ass of yours
have some nerve!
How about we take this outside?!
Fine by me.
Your big boobs and even bigger mouth are
long overdue for a good humbling, anyway.
Y-You guys...!
They really go for each other's throats
when they fight!
I came with Cecil 'cause I wanted to
see this play out!
No, no! We have to stop them!
Sorry, I couldn't if I tried!
Today's the day we settle this
once and for all!
I was just about to say that.
Though I hope you won't regret
humiliating yourself in front of Lord Hinata.
Wh-What do we do?!
Didja forget, Hinata?
How you used to stop 'em
when they got in an argument?
Maybe if someone were to
get down on his knees...
Everyone stop!
Cecil, May, I get why you
traveled to this world.
I know the risks of Bell being here.
I was also really confused when she
showed up in my apartment.
But...
During my time with Bell,
I realized that there are people here
who will accept her for who she is.
And more than anything, the fact that
she came here to visit me...
It made me really happy!
Hinata...
Yes, but if something were to happen...
If something goes wrong,
I'll take responsibility for it.
So please, let her stay!
Well, Cecil? Whaddya think?
I don't stand a chance against Lord Hinata...
Alright then.
Out of respect for Lord Hinata,
I will withhold my judgment for now.
Th-Thank you!
But do keep a few things in mind:
If something were to go wrong,
it would put us in danger,
and it could very well pose a threat
to Lord Hinata, too.
It's crucial that you remain as inconspicuous
as possible by using your discretion and—
Cecil, you're rambling again!
Pardon me.
Well then, we'll be going now.
See ya later!
Huh? Where are you going?
Seeing that we've reached
a temporary agreement,
there's no reason for us
to hang around here.
It's been so long since we
last saw each other.
You're welcome to stay and relax...
Well, as much as we'd like to...
We can't afford to linger in
this world for very long.
That's too bad...
Besides...
to interfere any further would put
our physical safety at risk.
"Physical safety"...?
Lord Hinata... may the gods protect you.
Oh, uh, thank you.
Okey-dokey, good luck!
"Good luck"...?
Hinata...
What's wrong, Bell?
Thank you, Hinata.
For sticking up for me.
I was really happy to hear...
that you want me here.
Bell...
And "taking responsibility"?
I had no idea you were giving so much
thought to our future together...
H-Huh?
If you're that serious about us,
then there's no need for me
to hold anything back, right?
"H-Hold back"...?
You shouldn't hold back, either.
Wha— Bell!
Quit it!
Hi-na-ta...
Playing hard to get?
Are you into that kind of thing?
N-No, I... Calm down, Bell!
I've stayed calm for too long!
You said... you'd take responsibility, right?
Hinata, look at me...
This is the lingerie you
bought for me the other day!
I have a lot to learn from you
in this new world, Hinata.
I can keep going 'cause I've got you.
You and I are destined to be together!
I know you'll step up to the plate...
Don't you want me, Hinata...?
Remember when you said
I had beautiful skin?
Look at it some more...
We can't do this... We aren't...
Feeling shy?
How adorable!
So soft...
Can you feel my heart pounding?
I belong to you, Hinata.
Touch me however you like.
Today's going to be the day, Hinata!
Let's have an in-depth conversation
about our future tonight.
All night long...
'Kay?
It's embarrassing if I'm the only one
who's naked. Take this off...
Bell...
Your skin is beautiful, too, Hinata...
Can't forget down here...
Why don't we say hello to mini-Hinata?
What in the hell...?!
May the gods protect you.
Cecil, you bitch!
Hinata?!
Dammit! The mood is ruined...!
Th-That was a close one...
Tsk, and after I managed to get
so close last night...
You're still upset about that?
Who could that be this early in the morning...?
Coming!
G'morning, you two!
Huh?!
For You
Starting today, we'll be your
next-door neighbors.
We look forward to getting to know you.
B-But why...?
We've been instructed to keep an eye on you
in case something goes wrong...
per government orders.
This'll be fun!
GO HOME!